that gives us a longitudinal data set that can really help us interpret the impact we're
seeing. And I think most important for us is the muscle manifestations. I know there's been a lot
of discussion as well about CNS, but I think in this particular disease,
what we're seeing is a lot of muscle manifestations. And I think that's a lot of
really matters is muscle mobility and managing those muscle-related manifestations. And that's
very much our focus. So having, I think, 54-week follow-up long-term data on a large cohort of
patients gives you a very robust read. And I think we feel confident that based on everything
we've seen in the phase two study, that we're set up well, as well as we can be towards that
phase three readout. Next question. Thank you. Your next question comes from the
line of Florent Cespedes from OdoBHF. Please go ahead.
Good afternoon. Thank you very much for taking my questions. Florent Cespedes from OdoBHF.
A big picture question for Vas. On your last slide, you highlighted that
there will be multiple readouts in H2 that could raise your mid-term to long-term growth outlook.
Maybe, Vas, could you be a little bit more specific and give us a bit more color or from where do you see that?
Do you see the potential upside coming from? Thank you.
Yeah, thanks, Florent. When you look at what we guided to last fall, our focus was very much
on what we had in hand and a probabilized view of our pipeline. And I think when then some of
these medicines, as they ultimately come forward and we unprobabilize, that can lead to significant
upsides versus where we are today. I think, obviously, the big readouts, not surprisingly,
I think to all of you, will certainly be Remibrutinib for the 5-year term. Remibrutinib in MS.
Remibrutinib in HS. Deldisran in DM1. We also believe, you know, Yinalumab and Firstline ITB
can be a billion-dollar-plus indication. I think Palacarcin will be significant. I think it will
take longer to build over time. And I think, overall, the combination of Palacarcin plus DIY235 will give us a very significant improvement.
Thank you.
again, opportunity. But in that kind of five-year term, I think that medicine will take time
to build up. But, you know, I think those are the medicines where, you know, if we see some wins,
it could allow us to, once we do the modeling, to reevaluate the 5% to 6% growth up to 2030